lenmar.com 2010-12-05

# Privacy

** ** | 

Lenmar Enterprises, Inc., a California Corporation, operates the Lenmar sites (including, without limitation, www.lenmar.com, www.lenmardirect.com, www.poweredbylenmar.com, www.batterycentral.com, and certain co-branded versions of its site under contract other third parties (collectively, the "Site"). You may only use the Site pursuant to the following terms and conditions, which you accept by your use of the Site. Lenmar, reserves the right to modify or revise these Terms of Use and/or Privacy Statement or its other policies at any time at its sole discretion. Any such modifications to the Terms of Use and Privacy Statement shall be effective within forty-eight (48) hours of being posted on the Site unless otherwise stated. Your continued use of the Site following Lenmar’s posting of any changes or modifications to these Terms of Use and/or Privacy Statement will constitute your acceptance of such changes or modifications. In the event that you do not agree to any of these Terms of Use and/or Privacy Statement, you should not continue to use the Site.

_**LICENSE AND SITE ACCESS**_

Lenmar grants you a non-exclusive right and license to access and use the Site for personal, and noncommercial purposes. This license does not include and strictly prohibits: any resale of the Site or its contents; any collection and use of any product listings, descriptions, or prices other than as expressly authorized herein; any derivative use of the Site or its contents; or any use of data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools. The Site, including its operation, interface and contents, are covered by United States copyright laws and international laws and treaties, and may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any unauthorized commercial purpose without the express prior written consent of Lenmar. Any unauthorized use shall immediately terminate the licenses and rights granted by Lenmar and any Licensors hereunder, and may subject you to civil and/or criminal prosecution. You are granted a limited, revocable, and nonexclusive right to create a hyperlink to any page of the Site so long as the link does not portray Lenmar, its subsidiaries, affiliates, Licensors, co-brand partners and other partners or its or their respective services in a false, misleading, derogatory or otherwise offensive or damaging manner. You may not use any Lenmar, Licensor, subsidiary, affiliate, co-brand partner, or other partner logo or other proprietary graphic or trademark as part of a link to the Site without first obtaining the express written consent of Lenmar, the subsidiary, affiliate, co-brand partner or other partner or Licensor (as applicable).

_**GENERAL**_

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

_**The Information We Collect:**_

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Lenmar websites. We do not require that you provide, nor do we collect, any personal information if you are just browsing the Site. On some pages, you can make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number

_**Dealers:**_

In addition to general information to process a transaction, credit/debit card information is collected securely. This information is retained for the period of time needed to complete the transaction and then purged from our system.

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Credit/Debit Card Information

_**The Way We Use Information:**_

We use the information you provide about yourself when registering your product only to identify and process future requests. We do not share this information with outside parties.

We use the information you provide in online request forms (information requests, feedback, warranty, and technical help) only in a manner necessary to provide the information requested. We do not share this information with outside parties.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with partners. For example, we may tell a partner that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of individuals searched for specific items, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

The Site contains links to web sites of third parties. Lenmar is not responsible for the actions of these third parties, including their privacy practices and any content posted on their web sites. We encourage you to review their privacy policies to learn more about what, why and how they collect and use personal information. Lenmar adheres to industry recognized standards to secure any personal information in our possession, and to secure it from unauthorized access and tampering.

Our web servers collect from Site visitors’ statistical information regarding what pages are visited, the date and time of the visits, how long it took a user to download a page, and the TCP/IP address of the user. These automated server functions do not collect this information in a manner intended to identify your individual use of the Site, nor do we use this information for any such purpose. This information is collected to assist us in maintaining a high quality site, as well as, providing necessary traffic information to our partners.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above.

_**Our Commitment To Data Security**_

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

_**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**_

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

_**How To Contact Us**_

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 1-800-424-2703 or send us an email at info@lenmar.com.
